[{"instructions":"Let's define a new operation +<sub>6</sub>. This operation will give us a way of combining two of the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 to get another one of them back. To perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result. (That's why the operation is called +<sub>6</sub>.) <br /><br />For example, 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2, because 3 + 5 = 8, and 8 is bigger than 6, so we subtract 6, and 8 - 6 = 2. So 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2.<br /><br />Similarly, 1 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5, because 1 + 4 = 5, and 5 is less than 6 so we leave it alone. <br /><br />Click \"Continue\" when you're ready to move on.","rt":139193,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":1,"time_elapsed":155082,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now try one on your own! What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6 </sub>,  you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":17591,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":2,"time_elapsed":172681,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 3 because 4 + 5 = 9 and 9 - 6 = 3.","rt":2887,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":3,"time_elapsed":175574,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":[" 5"],"rt":5576,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":4,"time_elapsed":181153,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 5 because 3 + 2 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":2338,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":5,"time_elapsed":183494,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":7655,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":6,"time_elapsed":191151,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0 because 1 + 5 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":1356,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":7,"time_elapsed":192511,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":4027,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":8,"time_elapsed":196540,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 2 because 1 + 1 = 2 and 2 is less than 6.","rt":1537,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":9,"time_elapsed":198080,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum  is 6 or  bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":4145,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":10,"time_elapsed":202227,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 3 because 3 + 0 = 3 and 3 is less than 6.","rt":1354,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":11,"time_elapsed":203586,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":3232,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":12,"time_elapsed":206821,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0 "},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 2 because 4 + 4 = 8 and 8 - 6 = 2.","rt":1206,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":13,"time_elapsed":208029,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":4023,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":14,"time_elapsed":212055,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 4 because 1 + 3 = 4 and 4 is less than 6.","rt":1377,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":15,"time_elapsed":213441,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember , to per form +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":4013,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":16,"time_elapsed":217457,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 1 because 4 + 3 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":1328,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":17,"time_elapsed":218790,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":10186,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":18,"time_elapsed":228980,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 5 because 0 + 5 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":10666,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":19,"time_elapsed":239650,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":4485,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":20,"time_elapsed":244137,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 1 because 2 + 5 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":1548,"trial_type":"feed back","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":21,"time_elapsed":245688,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"instructions":"Now we're going to discuss a couple special properties of this new operation, +<sub>6</sub> that we've learned. First, notice that the number 0 behaves in a special way under +<sub>6</sub>. Whenever we combine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back. We'll say that 0 is the <i>identity</i> under +<sub>6</sub>, because when you combine it with something it gives you that identical thing back.","rt":30394,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":22,"time_elapsed":276089,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now that we know 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>, we're going to make a new definition. We'll say that the <i>inverse</i> of a number is the thing that you combine with it to produce the identity. For example, 5 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 0, so we say 1 is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>6</sub>, (remember 0 is the identity un der +<su b>6</sub>). Similarly, 3 is its own inverse under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0.","rt":129594,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":23,"time_elapsed":405691,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! What is the inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":11000,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":24,"time_elapsed":416697,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub> is 2 because 4 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1417,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":25,"time_elapsed":418118,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> ( Remember , the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":8898,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":26,"time_elapsed":427019,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub> is 5 because 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1077,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":27,"time_elapsed":428099,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":4029,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":28,"time_elapsed":432131,"internal_chunk_id":"0- 0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub> is 3 because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1469,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":29,"time_elapsed":433602,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":4070,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":30,"time_elapsed":437674,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub> is 4 because 2 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":2259,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":31,"time_elapsed":439935,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 u nder +<s ub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":12573,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":32,"time_elapsed":452511,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub> is 0 because 0 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":22914,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":33,"time_elapsed":475431,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"instructions":"It is also possible to successively apply +<sub>6</sub>, and the operation can simply be performed starting with the left-most pair. For example, 2 +<sub>6</sub> 3 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 3.","rt":23529,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":34,"time_elapsed":498964,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0 "},{"instructions":"We have one last definition to learn today, using the successive operations we just learned. Let's start with an example. Under our operation +<sub>6</sub> we can make every other number using just 1: 2 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 3 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 4 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 5 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, and 0 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1. Because of this, we say that 1 is a <i>generator</i> under +<sub>6</sub>. <br /><br /> However, 2 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, and 0 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 2.","rt":98135,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":35,"time_elapsed":597102,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! Is 3 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a gener ator is  an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":14211,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":36,"time_elapsed":611323,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 = 3, 0 = 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 4, or 5 using just 3.","rt":1584,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":37,"time_elapsed":612911,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":4714,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":38,"time_elapsed":617628,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"feedback":"So rry, tha t's incorrect. 5 is a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 5 = 5, 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 3 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 2 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 1 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, and 0 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, so you can make all of the numbers under +<sub>6</sub> using 5","rt":90380,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":39,"time_elapsed":708011,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"question":"Is 4 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":21814,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":40,"time_elapsed":729832,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub >, becau se 4 = 4, 2 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, and 0 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 4.","rt":1461,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":41,"time_elapsed":731295,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"question":"Is 0 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":11131,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":42,"time_elapsed":742429,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 0 = 0, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 3, 4, or 5 using just 0.","rt":1148,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":43,"time_elapsed":743581,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"instructions":"Now we are going to ask you some questions about a new opera tion, +< sub>9</sub>, on the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8. It works exactly like +<sub>6</sub>, except now after adding the two numbers you subtract 9 if your result is 9 or greater. <br /><br />We'll give you one practice question with feedback to make sure you understand the new operation. After that, try to complete the remaining questions as accurately as possible.","rt":31634,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":44,"time_elapsed":775218,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Practice: What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":4784,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":45,"time_elapsed":780006,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5 = 1 because 5 + 5 = 10 and 10 - 9 = 1.","rt":1077,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":46,"time_elapsed":781086,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0 "},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>9</sub> 3?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":4105,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":47,"time_elapsed":785194,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 7 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":6088,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":48,"time_elapsed":791284,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>9</sub> 8?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":14948,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":49,"time_elapsed":806234,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":5242,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":50,"time_elapsed":811479,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 6 +<sub>9</sub> 6?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":4343,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":51,"time_elapsed":815825,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>9</sub> 1? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"5 because 4+1=5, 5<9 it is the answer.","response_history":["4 +","4 ","4+ 1 is ","4+ 1 is","4+ 1 i","4+ 1 ","4+ 1=","4+ 1","4+ ","4+1=5, 5<9 so subtract it from 9, 9-5=4","4+1=5, 5<9 it is the answer.","54+1=5, 5<9 it is the answer.","5.4+1=5, 5<9 it is the answer.","5. 4+1=5, 5<9 it is the answer.","5.  4+1=5, 5<9 it is the answer.","5  4+1=5, 5<9 it is the answer.","5 b 4+1=5, 5<9 it is the answer.","5 be 4+1=5, 5<9 it is the ans wer.","5  bec 4+1=5, 5<9 it is the answer.","5 beca 4+1=5, 5<9 it is the answer.","5 becau 4+1=5, 5<9 it is the answer.","5 because 4+1=5, 5<9 it is the answer."],"rt":86660,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":52,"time_elapsed":902491,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 8 +<sub>9</sub> 4? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"3 because 8+4=12, 12>9 so subtract 9 from 12. 12-9=3","response_history":["3 becaue","3 because 8+4=12, 12>9 so subtract it from 0","3 because 8+4=12, 12>9 so subtract it from 9, ","3 because 8+4=12, 12>9 so subtract 9 ","3 because 8+4=12, 12>9 so subtract 9","3 because 8+4=12, 12>9 so subtract 9 from 12. 12-9=3"],"rt":58997,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":53,"time_elapsed":961498,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is the identity under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got y our answ er.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0, I can't explain why.","response_history":["0, because","0, becaus","0, becau","0, beca","0, bec","0, be","0, b","0, IJ c","0, IJ ","0, IJ","0, I can't explain why."],"rt":56376,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":54,"time_elapsed":1017883,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":42222,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":55,"time_elapsed":1060111,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"7","response":"7","response_history":["7"],"rt":12219,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":56,"time_elapsed":1072334,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What  is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"6 because the inverse of a # is the # you combine it with to get the identity, which is 0.  3+6=9 and if answer is =9 than answer is 0","response_history":["7, ","7,","7","6 because the inverse of a n","6 because the inverse of a # is the $","6 because the inverse of a # is the # you combie","6 because the inverse of a # is the # you combine it with to get the identy","6 because the inverse of a # is the # you combine it with to get the identt","6 because the inverse of a # is the # you combine it with to get the identity, which is 0.  3 =","6 because the inverse of a # is the # you combine it with to get the identity, which is 0.  3 ","6 because the inverse of a # is the # you combine it with to get the identity, which is 0.  3+6 ","6 because the inverse of a # is the # you combine it with to get the ident ity, whi ch is 0.  3+6=9 and if answer is =9 than answer is 0"],"rt":89396,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":57,"time_elapsed":1161734,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"Is 2 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No, because you can't make all of the sums by adding 2 to 2 repeatedly.","response_history":["No, because yu","No, because you can't make all of the s","No, because you can't make all of the sums by add","No, because you can't make all of the sums by ad","No, because you can't make all of the sums by adding 2 to 2 repeatedly."],"rt":80142,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":58,"time_elapsed":1241883,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"Is 3 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No, because it is not possible to get all of the numbers 0-5 as answers using only the number 3 as an additive.","response_history":["no, ","no,","no","n","No, becasu","No, becas","No, because it s","No, because it is not o","No, because it is not possible to get all of the numbers 0-5 as answers using only the number 6 as an additive.","No, because it is not possible to get all of the numbers 0-5 as answers using only the number 3 as an additive."],"rt":86844,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":59,"time_elapsed":1328735,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"yes, because you can use 5 to generate every other number below 9","response_history":["yes, because you can use 5 to generate every other number below 9"],"rt":327273,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":60,"time_elapsed":1656025,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"Is 6 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"no, because you can't use 6 to generate every number under 9","response_history":["no, becu","no, because you can't use 6 to generalte","no, because you can't use 6 to generalt","no, because you can't use 6 to general","no, because you can't use 6 to generate aever","no, because you can't use 6 to generate aeve","no, because you can't use 6 to generate aev","no, because you can't use 6 to generate ae","no, because you can't use 6 to generate a","no, because you can't use 6 to generate ","no, because you can't use 6 to generateevery","no, because you can't use 6 to generateever","no, because you can't use 6 to generateeve","no, because you can't use 6 to generateev","no, because you can't use 6 to generatee","no, because you can't use 6 t o genera te every number unt","no, because you can't use 6 to generate every number under 6","no, because you can't use 6 to generate every number under 9"],"rt":92166,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":61,"time_elapsed":1748199,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"instructions":"Now we'd like to ask you some questions about +<sub>n</sub>, where n could be any postive counting number. For example, n could be 3, or n could be any other counting number you can think of. If you need to write the operation, you can use \"+_n\", and your answers can include n to stand in for the arbitrary value if necessary.","rt":27555,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":62,"time_elapsed":1775762,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of 1 under +<sub>n</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-1","response":"1 + _n = 0","response_history":["- + ","- +","- ","-","1 + _n = 0"],"rt":225519,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":63,"time_elapsed":2001287,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of an element x under +<sub>n</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-x","response":"x + _n = 0 because the inverse of the number is the answer that will equal 0","response_history":["x = ","x =","x ","x + _n = x","x + _n = 0 ","x + _n = 0 because the inverse of the number will equal ","x + _n = 0 because the inverse of the number will equal","x + _n = 0 because the inverse of the number will equal","x + _n = 0 because the inverse of the number w","x + _n = 0 because the inverse of the number is the answer that will equal 0"],"rt":122179,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":64,"time_elapsed":2123473,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"Is there a pattern to which elements are generators? How can yo u know i f an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub> without seeing whether it can make all the elements?.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I haven't found the pattern if there is one.","response_history":["I haven't found the pattern if there is one."],"rt":47643,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":65,"time_elapsed":2171122,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an odd number, it must be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"True","response_history":["True"],"rt":97988,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":66,"time_elapsed":2269119,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an even number, it must not be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"Tr ue","response_history":["True"],"rt":7200,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":67,"time_elapsed":2276325,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must divide n.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"True","response_history":["True"],"rt":76062,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":68,"time_elapsed":2352390,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a multiple of a divisor of n. Please explain in words why your answer is corret.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"True","response":"Only odd numbers seem to be generators, unless it can be divided evenly into +n.  Once it can be evenly divided into it, the same numbers keep coming up in a pattern.","response_history":["W","Only odd numbers seem to be generators, n l","Only  odd numbers seem to be generators, n","Only odd numbers seem to be generators, unless it is div","Only odd numbers seem to be generators, unless it is di","Only odd numbers seem to be generators, unless it is d","Only odd numbers seem to be generators, unless it is a ","Only odd numbers seem to be generators, unless it is a","Only odd numbers seem to be generators, unless it is divisible","Only odd numbers seem to be generators, unless it is","Only odd numbers seem to be generators, unless it i","Only odd numbers seem to be generators, unless it cna","Only odd numbers seem to be generators, unless it cn","Only odd numbers seem to be generators, unless it can be divided evenly into the","Only odd numbers seem to be generators, unless it can be divided evenly into th","Only odd numbers seem to be generators, unless it can be divided evenly into t","Only odd numbers seem to be generators, unless it can be divided evenly into +n.  Once it can be evenly divided into it, only","O nly odd  numbers seem to be generators, unless it can be divided evenly into +n.  Once it can be evenly divided into it, onl","Only odd numbers seem to be generators, unless it can be divided evenly into +n.  Once it can be evenly divided into it, on","Only odd numbers seem to be generators, unless it can be divided evenly into +n.  Once it can be evenly divided into it, oth","Only odd numbers seem to be generators, unless it can be divided evenly into +n.  Once it can be evenly divided into it, ot","Only odd numbers seem to be generators, unless it can be divided evenly into +n.  Once it can be evenly divided into it, o","Only odd numbers seem to be generators, unless it can be divided evenly into +n.  Once it can be evenly divided into it, the same numbers c","Only odd numbers seem to be generators, unless it can be divided evenly into +n.  Once it can be evenly divided into it, the same numbers keep a","Only odd numbers seem to be generators, unless it can be divided evenly into + n.  Once  it can be evenly divided into it, the same numbers keep coming up in a pattern."],"rt":75866,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":69,"time_elapsed":2428262,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"If an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is its inverse a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Always","response":"Never","response_history":["Never"],"rt":93721,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":70,"time_elapsed":2521990,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never? Please explain in words why your answer is corret.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"sometimes","response":"Never, but I can't be positive and I can't explain why.  ","response_history":["Nv","Never, but I can't be positive and i ","Never, but I can't be positive and i","Never, but I can't be positive and I can't explain why.  "],"rt":151989,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":71,"time_elapsed":2673985,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"If an element x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Never","response":"Never","response_history":["Never"],"rt":128704,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":72,"time_elapsed":2802696,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"instructions":"We would like to ask you some questions about your background. Please press \"Continue\" to continue.","rt":2256,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":73,"time_elapsed":2804958,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is you r age?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"49","response_history":["49"],"rt":3077,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":74,"time_elapsed":2808039,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is your level of education?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Did not graduate high school","High school diploma","Some college, no degree","Associates Degree","Bachelors Degree","Some graduate school, no degree","Masters Degree","Doctorate, M.D., etc."],"correct_response":"","response":"High school diploma","response_history":["High school diploma"],"rt":3729,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":75,"time_elapsed":2811771,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is the most advanced math class you've completed? If you have multiple classes and you're not sure which one is most advanced, please list them.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Prob ably 11th grade algebra.","response_history":["Probably 11th grade algebra."],"rt":19333,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":76,"time_elapsed":2831107,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of modular arithmetic?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - never heard of it","response_history":["1 - never heard of it"],"rt":7884,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":77,"time_elapsed":2838994,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of a mathematical group?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not o ften or  recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - never heard of it","response_history":["1 - never heard of it"],"rt":5389,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":78,"time_elapsed":2844386,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you learned something from this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":12978,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":79,"time_elapsed":2857367,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you understood the concepts in this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":3909,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":80,"time_elapsed":2861278,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Did you enjoy this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"3 - definitely","response_history":["3 - definitely"],"rt":2558,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":81,"time_elapsed":2863839,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is your gender?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Female","Male","Other"],"correct_response":"","response":"Female","response_history":["Female"],"rt":2293,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":82,"time_elapsed":2866136,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is/are your native language(s)? (The languages spoken in your household when you were a child.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"English","response_history":["English"],"rt":6799,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":83,"time_elapsed":2872938,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Did you use pen and paper at any point on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Yes, continually.","response_history":["Yes, continually."],"rt":9058,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":84,"time_elapsed":2881999,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Do you have any comments on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"no","response_history":["no"],"rt":7102,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":85,"time_elapsed":2889104,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"}]